promojunkie.com 2015-04-08

# Privacy Statement

## Your Privacy

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.

## Google Adsense and the DoubleClick DART Cookie

Google, as a third party advertisement vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on this site. The use of DART cookies by Google enables them to serve adverts to visitors that are based on their visits to this website as well as other sites on the internet.

To opt out of the DART cookies you may visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following url <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html> Tracking of users through the DART cookie mechanisms are subject to Google's own privacy policies.

Other Third Party ad servers or ad networks may also use cookies to track users activities on this website to measure advertisement effectiveness and other reasons that will be provided in their own privacy policies, PromoJunkie has no access or control over these cookies that may be used by third party advertisers.

## Collection of Personal Information

PromoJunkie may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways, including through online forms for ordering products and services, and other instances where Users are invited to volunteer such information. PromoJunkie may also collect information about how end-users use our web site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by the pages of the website or the domains from which users originate. We may use "cookies" to track how Users use our Web site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the Users' PC and use to identify the User should they visit the Web site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us through our Web site. When visiting PromoJunkie, the IP address used to access the site will be logged along with the dates and times of access. This information is purely used to analyze trends, administer the site, track users movement and gather broad demographic information for internal use. Most importantly, any recorded IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

## How We Use Information

PromoJunkie may use personally identifiable information collected through our web site to contact Users regarding products and services offered by PromoJunkie only. PromoJunkie may also use information collected through our Web site for research regarding the effectiveness of the Web site and the marketing, advertising and sales efforts of PromoJunkie. At no time will PromoJunkie's database of users ever be sold to any entity for the purpose of marketing or mailing lists.

## Links to third party Websites

We have included links on this site for your use and reference. We are not responsible for the privacy policies on these websites. You should be aware that the privacy policies of these sites may differ from our own.

## Disclosure of Information

Any information provided to PromoJunkie is solely used for internal purposes and will not be sold or distributed in any fashion to outside parties.

## Information Maintenance

Information about Users that is maintained on our systems is protected using industry standard security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that the information submitted to, maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.

## Changes to this Privacy Statement

The contents of this statement may be altered at any time, at our discretion.

If you have any questions regarding the privacy policy of PromoJunkie then please submit a ticket via our Support Center.
